

Kristian Gerkman

Piikkirinne 1 A1, 01650 Vantaa +358 45 263 8239 kristiangerkman1@gmail.com <u>Github</u> LinkedIn

EDUCATION

Metropolia, Information technology bachelor's Degree 2020-Present

University of Helsinki, Fullstack WebDev MOOC

In this course I learned about MERN-stack and how to build single page application with it. I also learned about testing, project structure, webpack, redux state management and a lot of other things about JavaScript and web development in general.

University of Helsinki, Java-programming MOOC

In this course I learned all the fundamental things about Java and object-oriented programming in general.

Omnia, Information technology 2016 - 2019

In Omnia I learned to build websites using PHP and MySQL and learned to use Linux for development. I also used a lot of time to decide what I want to do, in the end I settled on web development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frantic, Jan 2019 – Jun 2019

I did Omnia's on-the-job learning period at Frantic as site builder trainee. My work was consisted of updating and adding files to CMS, I also updated CSS files that were not in the CMS.

City of Vantaa, Jun 2017 - Aug 2017

Summer job in Myyrmäki's Library as librarian trainee. Whilst I was there, I helped customers with their IT problems and did some logistic work and used the library's database system

PROFILE

I'm easy going 19-years-old Finnish information technologies engineering student in Metropolia and I'm looking for a part time job, that I can do alongside my studies.

I'm keen on learning all kinds of stuff, it really doesn't matter what it is, but it must be somewhat interesting. I especially like coding and technologies just for that reason; I can always learn new interesting stuff and it never ends. I also like the problem solving and mathematics aspect of coding.

On my spare time I code, go to the gym, hang out with my friends, learn from interesting Youtube videos, play guitar and draw.

LANGUAGES

Finnish (native) English (fluid)

SKILLED IN

React development Java development PHP development Linux GIT

FUNDAMENTALS IN

C & C++ development Python development